you're still down here mistress how come
would you like me
to call for the maids to prepare a bath for you
and upper chambers
i can arrange that for you then yes of course mistress
you called for me my lady the bath tree well
you need help getting settled in for bed oh
i could not help you myself
but perhaps the ladies
mate could comb your hair and get you relaxed for the night
i shall call her for you now
and i can leave my candle light on
if you need any further evening affairs for me to attend to
yes mistress
oh
i couldn't step into your bedroom and comb your hair myself
that is not right of me to impose on your space
at this late of hour
i can find you one of the mates
i hum
of course
mistress if it is with your quest for me to comb your hair
then i shall be accommodating towards you
how you sit in front of your vanity then
i couldn't sit on your bed mistress
they will not be appropriate for me to do so
i guess if it makes you more comfortable
and we can sit on your bed
yes mistress of course
i'm sorry come again my lady
you want to take your rope off
if you want to take it off and change into your evening entire
i can step off the room so you can change
you are taking it off now
should i not leave the room
yes
mistress
i'll stay here then and continue to comb your hair
if you feel more comfortable
nude as long as you are comfortable
what's that mistress
do i think your body is beautiful
why yes
you're a gorgeous lady the master should be lucky of himself
do i think you're sexy
that is not my place to answer
oh
uh
you have turned around and you're fully naked in front of me
do you no longer need your hair combed anymore
i can let you rest for the night
i'll just get up and let you rest then
or not
mistress what are you doing
my
you're very strong
especially
when you have me pinned down with your body on top of mine
this isn't right
though my lady
you're nude
and i shouldn't be even in your presence when you're like this
you're married to a very kind loving husband
i know you do miss him and it must be hard being alone
but he is my master
and i cannot disobey him by being in this position
王yes
i know an easy way i must listen to your orders mistress
but i cannot be doing this
i mean i shouldn't be doing this
oh mistress
you do feel lonely
isn't that correct i suppose
he has been away for so long and since then have been all alone
this bed every night by
yourself
i will follow your orders then stay in your bed
i am at your mercy mistress
i mean i cannot move with you on top of me like this
anyways
you're police with this position was this plan all along
of course
no more questions i'll just be here to serve you
i do think your sexy mistress the sexiest woman
i've ever seen
if i'm honest
your curves are stunning with those fantastic breasts
and lucious hips
i'll admit i stare far too off than than what's appropriate
i've always wanted to know what's underneath
your dresses and my lady
it is far more than perfection can ever hold
you're beyond the goddess
you're beyond angelic
i am lost for words for the beauty that you hold
let me please you however you choose mistress
hmm
i'll start with your wet slit
then
oh my
you taste amazing
i've never tasted something so sweet
graph etra Bristol liquor lips
thank you mistress
you wanna use my face to orgasm oh
mistress i want you to use me however you need me
it will be a privilege to have your orgasm in my mouth
your juices are incredible
you are so beautiful
oh please use me for your own pleasure i'm at your disposal
i'll help you reach as many orgasm as your body craves
that's it keep going
i want to taste your orgasm
please give it to me
i want to see you
explode yourself right on top of me just like that i'm
not done until you are mistress ride my face
as much as you need to
i've never witnessed something as beautiful and sexy
as your orgasms
watching you go into a blissful trance as your body
lets go of everything you lose your control to my touch
please keep going for me
oh you're getting off my face now
oh mistress you want me to penetrate you
i shall and blend my pens for you then if that is what you want
or you can too
are you pleased with my nudity is this
what you wanted enjoy seeing my heart direction for you
it is yours to use my job is to please you
oh
yes mistress take my throbbing shaft inside you oh
god
you know what
you're doing you're so good mistress this feels so good
no
oh
yes of course yes
of course
i'm sorry for enjoying it so much
i cannot help it but he has mistress
i know this is about your pleasure only
let me grab you like this
let you relax and enjoy me inside you that way
i can just keep thrusting into you like this
hold my hips like that so you can control how deep i go
that's it mistress
i love how you're gripping my body and using me
for your own pleasure
you are so good at this
you know just what you're doing
i
can go faster for you
how does this feel
am i pleasing you
yes mistress i won't stop until you come
i can feel myself pulsing against your walls
you are so tight it is incredible
my head is just hitting your g spot with every thrust i feel it
my thighs are against yours stay close this is what you want
isn't it to feel the closeness of someone again
oh mistress i am so lucky
it is an honor to be inside you
oh
please come more for me
mistress please you deserve to orgasm
you deserve to use me for your pleasure hmm
that's it let me slide deeper inside you oh
keep going i can feel your clenchy
yes
bring me closer to you
yes that's it let me feel your orgasm around every inch of me oh
mistress i think i'm going to no
i can't no
ah ah ah
i can't
oh god
i can't stop myself
huh
i am so sorry
yeah
oh god i just work at something all over your body
yes mistress i know i didn't have your permission to come
i am so sorry
what
i am to be punished for my orgasm yes
of course mistress i'll do what you say
i'll listen to your comments better so pay whatever
it is you want me to steal
i realized i made a mess i can clean it up
with my tongue yes
mistress that isn't a problem
let me just get close to your beautiful naked body
and taste my own orgasm and clean it off you
hmm
it does taste good mistress
thank you for accepting my apology
i'll make sure i get every drop of my seat off your body
i know it is not my body to enjoy i just couldn't help myself
you are so sexy
i am weak and could not control myself around you
but if i just look here
that should be it
i think i got all of it off of you your body tasted
just as sweet thank you for letting me like it
i know it is obeyed your orders mistress
but it was a privilege to see you like this
it was wrongful for me to orgasm with you like how
i did but i hope that tonight has fulfilled the need you had
and that you are satisfied with me mistress
i am at your service for whenever you acquire
i am yours at any moment of the day
i do think it is time for me to leave your chambers
and let you rest
we have both had quite a night
and i should get back to my room before anyone notice my absence
what's that my lady
of course i could do this again tomorrow night
i am forever at your mercy i shall be looking forward to it
then good night mistress