so
are you warming up to the idea
I know I know
you've already told me the fantasy is hot
but what do you think about making it real
I mean we got this far
you're here sip in the drink I bought you
you wore the shoes we've talked about
and I can smell your perfume
huh
no I
I understand
it is a big jump from writing each other filthy things
from the pictures we sent
even
from being here to going there
my place or hotel room
the bathroom of this bar
and Nelly
you know where there is
no no I get it
I really do
you've got boundaries
even if you've pushed them more than you planned
I guess
I'm not enough to make you throw them out completely am
I I know
you need a distraction
and hey this
has been fun
look I'm still down for the fantasies
you're more nah
elaborate than some of the other girls I message
I can't deal with
just jerking off your
pictures and thinking about the filthy things you've
said while I fucked my girlfriend or whatever
I don't know
in here
no one can hear what I'm saying
plus they're all hammered
isn't that why you wanted to meet here in the first
place
find some shit hole to grab a drink with me so
no one will see you
I'm teasing you silly
it's fine
I think we could have had a lot of fun together
but of course
I'm not gonna pressure you
and honestly I expected you to get cold feet
why don't we just have one more drink left this off
talk about
sports and then go back to the usual
pretend we never met up
yeah I'll just go grab drinks
don't take too long
haha
what do you want
cool
you know what
no you little bitch
I thought about it
and you've teased me too much to get away within
I'm sorry I can't do this
be
quiet
this is what you said you wanted isn't
it this is the exact scenario it played out
the kind of thing you talked about
in those ridiculous recordings
turning you into a come ragging a public bathroom
you say you're not a cheater
that's a laugh
anyone would have a conscience with callwell even done
cheating
but if technicalities will make you feel better
I'll just rape you
strip
fucking do it
the panties too
you dumb cunt
Jesus you are
I mean
how long did you spend taking those pictures
trying to get the exact right angle
what did you think was going to happen when we fucked
you've seen pictures of my wife
you had to know you didn't measure up
of course she's better than you
I know it you know it
how about you tell me how
yeah
put your clothes back on
no we are not done here
it's just your body isn't going
to make this faster for either of us
that outfit was it supposed to be sexy
you really don't know what you're doing do you
I mean the
skirt makes it so I'll be
able to use your holes without seam
more than I want to
so that works
but that's about all that does
bend over the sink slut
there
skirt pulled up
panties to the side
I can see the best parts of you
then you can see your stupid face in the mirror
look at yourself
reach back and take your panties off slut
let me see them
you made a mess out of these
didn't you
yeah you did
I'll wipe them off on your ass before
open your mouth
your juice is glistening on your slit
panties stuffed in your mouth
you're starting to look like a real whore
how do they taste
huh
hard to talk with your mouthful isn't
it
you've talked too much already though
time to see if your pussy can measure up to
any of the chatter
I'm thinking not
don't you dare shut those eyes
I want you to watch yourself moan
around those filthy panties
while I
slide a finger into that cut
this isn't going how you thought it would
you just wanted the attention
wanted someone to tell you that you were pretty
enough to fuck
wanted to feel wanted
you didn't really plan to follow through
you were just going to talk and talk
and talk and waste my time
you are soaking wet though
you can tell yourself it's rape
but we both know different
you're going to fucking
love feeling me slamming to your cunt
like this
oh
you want me to stop
that's bullshit and you know it
that's why you always told yourself isn't it
it's not cheating if you rapes me
that's why this stupid fantasy makes you come every
single time
that's why your
cun is wet and your hips are moving and you're
starting to cry
isn't it
you want it and the only way you can get it and still
sleep at night
is if you goat someone into taking you
how does my dick feel a little slut
you can't talk with your mouth gag like that pity
but
I know it's bigger than your husband's
are you grateful
you should be
getting fucked this good
you're a lucky little bitch to get to be my rape slut
I know it feels good
I've made enough women come
I don't have to hear you say it
I can feel your pussy dripping and
clenching around my cock while I thrust
ah
no I want you
you've got to realize that
your husband doesn't or he'd make you come
I don't or I'd put a little more effort into you than a
quick fucking public bathroom
you are a warm cut
that's it
a wet little hole for me to stick my cock into and pump
away until I shoot all over your sloppy pussy
doesn't matter how filthy you are
how hard you try and make yourself seem interesting
that's all you are ever going to be
you hold my attention for what
maybe a few months
if you're lucky
probably a lot less
then I'll have used you completely
and you'll have to debase yourself even
more to get your fix
your husband is a nice guy isn't he
sweet
takes care of you
you don't deserve him
and you don't want him
you are so fucked in the head
you only want someone who will fuck with your head
I'll do that but you haven't earned sex like this
haven't proven you are worth getting fucked this good
you know how
stupid you sounded when we were planning this meeting
trying to sound all coy
talking about chemistry
you don't need chemistry with a comrade
you pretentious fucking bitch
that's what you are
you know that
say it
say
it
ah fuck
this is getting you off isn't
it hear me tell you the truth about what you are
well I'm working on your whole
ah
go ahead and come whenever you want little whore
but do not think I'm going to stop when you do
this isn't about you coming
it's about me taking what
I'm old after all your teasing
yeah
fucking coming if you want I don't care
you just wish I'd started on your ass don't you
that's why you are arcing your back
sticking it out
why don't you wiggle it around
oh
God
you look so stupid
I'll stick a finger in there
oh fuck
that's tight
and you told me you would take my dick off your asshole
even more bullshit
taking such a big game with no experience to back it up
I'll break you
and you're pathetic enough that you think you can
actually want that
spit the panties out into the sink
tell me you want to be broken
say it or
louder
tell me you want me to rape you until you're a shaking
compliant mess
you want it in your ass little bitch
wanna prove you can take it
your pussy wasn't going to make me come anyways
you're too wet
I'm sliding in too easily
beg for it beg for this dicking her asshole
yeah
put the panties back in her mouth
and then reach her hands back and spread her
cheeks for me
show me exactly where you want my cock
just like that
show me that tight little fuckle
keep spreading your cheeks while I push in
oh God
you're lucky my dick is so wet from your cut
this is still going to hurt
but
just bit down on those panties and take it
go ahead you can scream into them
no one's gonna hear you in this bar
that's why you chose it
you knew this was gonna happen
look at yourself
taking a dick off your ass in a public bathroom
you think this makes you special
you want to be the good girl in the whore
that's not how it works
the good girl is the one I'm proud of
the one whose hand all hold in public
you're not a good girl
not even a good person
you're a slut who thinks she's a hell a lot
more interesting than
she is
your average at best
you think I'm jerking off with your
cut right in now because you are what
pretty
smart
special
no and here's the truth
most men will fuck just about anything once
especially if their friends are gonna see
you're a tonight's piece of ass
and finding a girl who is equally hell much more pretty
won't be hard at all
you're probably gonna
think about this idea every time you
shove a fake cock up that pussy to make yourself come
but I'm gonna use you up
drain my balls inside you and move on with my life
you want that
want me to come huh
better fucking beg for it
you can spit the panties out
again and tell me how much you want me to come
think you deserve it
not inside you
you don't I'm gonna pull out and come all over your ass
stain your clothes so
everyone this bar will see what a slut you are
so your
husband will see your cum covered holes and know the
truth
tell me when I walked out of here
shaking and crying and smelling like my cum
come on
beg
what are you waiting for
a kiss
go home
try and hide the comb stains on that cheap skirt
tell your husband you were out with friends
think of some way to explain those bite parts
if he even pays enough attention to you to notice
don't forget your place
little come slut
and message me the next time you remember
how pathetic you are