all right come on baby girl
let's get you in bed
what do you mean
you're not tired you fell asleep in the car
yes
you did you got drool all over my window you were knocked out
all that dancing must have really taken a lot out of you
no i will not take you back to the club
i know your friends are there
but you are done for the night now will you
because those friends when you get so drunk
that you had to call your ex
boyfriend who
you haven't spoken to in months to come rescue you
and because i'm an idiot
i dropped everything
and drove across town at two a m to pick you up
and bring you home
but the party's over
babe no be a good girl and get in bed
no seriously you're gonna find me on this come on
don't make me force you into bed look you called me
because you knew
i would save you
because despite everything
you so trust me more than anyone else right
then please just don't you want to be a good girl for me
oh you are not a good girl anymore
huh
yeah
that much is obvious
what i'm just saying the girl
i knew she didn't act
like she would never get this drunk or wear that kind of dress
or be caught dead in that club with those girls
i don't even know what those girls are
oh well i'm sorry but if they are the reason
you're acting like this
your new friends are clearly a bad influence on you
and i don't know who
you're trying to impress with all this bullshit but
good girls don't act like this
i'm talking about
no
you know what we're not doing this right now get in pet
no i am not doing this with you just lay the fuck down
go to sleep and when you wake up tomorrow
you can go right back to pretending i don't exist
stop stop trying to argue with me
will you just stop being such a brat for ten seconds and just
go to bed little girl
now
if you don't want me to talk to you like a little girl
then stop acting like one grow up and do as i say either
you get in that bed
or i'll put you
there myself understood
that's it thank you
god look at yourself you're a mess you know that right
you can't even walk in a straight line
so what were you thinking
anyone could have taken advantage of you at that club
and you wouldn't have been able to stop them
you're lucky you called me
ah fuck
i can't just leave you like this
what the hell are you doing to yourself
girl
this
isn't you
the clubs the parties the clubs you are not this girl
you were never like this before
when we were
together
oh
don't look at me like that you know exactly what i mean
as soon as we broke up you became someone else
yes you did
i still follow you on Instagram
i see you going out
every night wearing these sexy little dresses
dancing up on random
dudes like you don't care about anyone
you are so different when we were together
you were real and the longer you keep up this whole bad bitch
act the more you gonna get hurt
because i know
you're hurting yourself girl and for what Instagram likes
vip sections bottle service and fake friendships that shit
doesn't matter you are all that matters
not this you but the real you the you i fell in love with
do you want to know
my first thought was when i saw her name pop up on my phone
finally
finally she's come to her senses
finally she realizes that we're meant to be together
finally she's ready to stop running around acting
like some desperate
little slut and just be herself be a good girl my good girl
but i was strong and despite everything i can't get over you
i still came to save you because i guess i'm just
wait are you oh shit no don't cry please don't cry
i'm sorry i i didn't mean that
scoot over
come here just let me hold you okay
put your hand on my chest
that's it curl up into me
there you go
that's a good girl
shh
it's okay you don't have to cry i'm sorry all right
i had to mean any of the stuff i know
you're still the same girl i fell in love with
that's better take a deep breath for me
and another
good girl
i didn't mean it
i just miss you
i miss talking to you and dancing with you
and holding you like this
i miss you so much
it hurts
i scroll through your pictures
and my chest aches the idea of you out
there all alone with no one to look out for you it scares me
it's like you've forgotten what really matters
and i worry about you girl
look up at me
god
that mascara is running all across your cheeks
let me wipe those tears away for you baby
i will always take care of you you know that right
i will always be here for you
fuck
you look so beautiful when you cry
i missed you i missed you so much
oh fuck
i need you right now i know i shouldn't but fuck i need you
i've been waiting for this since that day you left
i missed you so much
little girl daddy missed you
wait what's wrong
why are you pulling back
stop i'm not stopping
you don't want me to stop this is why you called me isn't
it because you missed me too i know you did
stop trying to pull away you know you can't get away from me
you are so small that i can wrap my arms
all the way around you press your body against mine grab this
as you love to show off so much
and force you to grind yourself against me
do you feel that baby
i'm so fucking hard for you
stop scorming little girl
you are so drunk you're gonna hurt yourself
if you keep struggling like this
or daddy's gonna have to hurt you
but maybe that's what you want
you always did like a bite of pain and you are so much
more obedient after i've hurt you a little
is that what you need
you need daddy to pull up the hem of the stress and chest
speak this juicy ass don't you
no this isn't what you need
are you sure little girl
because i think you need a good spanking
i think you need to pay for being such a bad girl
fuck i love watching that ass bounce under my hands
you've been a very bad girl without me around haven't you
but that's all over now you're mine you'll always be mine
kiss me back
come on
you need me i know you do nobody else can do this for you
oh you don't need me
really let me push these panties to the side and see
if you don't need me
why are you so fucking wet
good girls don't get with this wet unless
they want it so either you're a lying
or you really become a desperate little slow without me around
which is it little girl
fuck
i need you
way back i'm not even going to get undressed i'll trust
fuck your pussy is even tighter than i remember oh that's it
that is gonna take it slow for you baby girl
i remember how you like it slow and deep
intense and intimate just like this
your body pin underneath mine surrounded by me
my weight pressing you down
as my clock slides in an elephant tight little pussy
god i missed this pussy did you miss me
tell me how much you missed daddy's cock
no you didn't miss me
i know that's not true why are you lying to me
stop saying no
you need me
you need me to save you to remind you of who
you really are to keep you in line
you need something to make you good ah
you're gonna be good for me aren't you ah
fine
if you won't say yes to me
i'll just cover your mouth
because even though your lips might be saying no
your body knows the truth
i can feel how wet you are
you're already dripping around my cock
your body knows that no one else can take care of you the way
i do
huh
are you trying to struggle
stop that little girl you
don't have to fight this anymore just lay there and fucking
take it
take it like a good girl
good girls don't lie
they don't say no and they do not fight back
they don't leave the house looking
like a slut or get so drunk
they're just begging someone to take advantage of them
but you are done being a bad girl
because you are a good girl and you know it oh
that other bullshit that's over now
no more parties no new friends from now on
you're gonna let me take care of you
that is gonna take good care of his sweet little girl yeah
that's right
just lie there and take it take it like the good girl you are
fuck
i'm sorry but i can't hold back any longer
i know you like it slow but your pussy feels so good
i can't wait anymore i need to come inside you
and i needed to feel you come all over my clock
oh that's it
baby girl just take it take all of it
fuck
that's good
no don't close your eyes look at me baby
oh
are you crying again
why are you crying baby
don't cry you don't have to cry anymore daddy's got you now
he knows exactly how to make you feel good
how to make you come
you're gonna come for me aren't you nod your head for me
that's right you know you can't hold back when
i tell you to come
you can't hold anything back from me
and i can't hold back from you
i love you i never stopped loving you
and i'm not going to let you get hurt anymore you are mine
ugh
i still love you the real you
you're still my good little girl aren't you
and i'm still your daddy
you don't have to cry anymore you don't have to pretend anymore
daddy's here baby girl
i will always be here for you
you are the best thing that ever happened to me
you are the best
i've ever had and i know you still love me
too
don't you want to be a good girl for me
don't you want to come all over daddy's cock
like a good girl
oh fuck
i'm gonna come be a good girl and come with daddy
come all over daddy's cock
oh
that's it come for me scream into my hand
give me everything good girl
啊
i'm so glad you called me tonight babygirl
i miss you so much come here
i'm not ready to let you go yet
we don't need to change clothes or clean up
you can just fall asleep in my arms like this
and tomorrow morning
we'll talk about
getting rid of all these new clothes and new friends so
you can trust meme yourself again
be mine again
you're my everything you know that
you're all i've ever wanted the best i've
ever had and you're gonna be the best little girl for me forever