it's been another one of those days hasn't
it rushed off your feet with working chores
stressed everything is just weighing down on you before
you even noticed it let your guard down
of course i couldn't resist slipping
right through the gap in your defenses
poking and protting teasing the poor overworked mind of yours
and corrupting the thoughts in your head
it never takes much effort for me to do that though does it
oh that's right all that poking took your words away
didn't it silly me
how could i forget that
that doesn't mean it's completely empty up there though is it
we both know that this isn't
the first time
i've sent you off
the bed dripping wet
and the night had full of thoughts of what i do to
or with you is a sweetheart
or would you prefer slut
of course you would now that we've got you here
what do you think is going to happen
oh you poor thing you can barely
even focus on the present let alone the future can you slut
always two steps behind me
and i'm almost certain that there's no point in me
asking you anything in this state
concentrate
do i have your attention now
as i was saying what's next
do you have any ideas
or are you just going to lie there
with that dumb look on your face
huh
of course you are it's what i do to you isn't it
you just can't help yourself around me
can you no need to answer
all i need you to do is listen
i'm sure you can find a brainsaw or two for that at least
good girl
hmm
maybe we should start slow hands on your tips
them a nice firm squeeze for me make sure i get a good view
well done that's perfect i guess you can follow instructions
keep going i want to see those nipples not nice and stiff for me
now open your legs for me
put everything on display like a good little slut
and look at that you're already so wet for me
i haven't even touched you
and you are thoroughly soaked
and was that a moan
you're already getting off on this
aren't you you pathetic slut
i'm there thinking about all the things i might do to you
all the ways i might use you
is really hoping
i'll break the tension and touch you
hoping that you'll feel my hand run up your inner thigh
and pull those trenched panties to one side
maybe you're hoping
they'll give you permission to wrap your hand around my cock
my fingers hook into your greedy little cut too bad
you'll have no such luck tonight are going to lie back
and listen
when i'm done talking
then you can come do you understand
i didn't quite hear that can you say it again for me
that's better
no let's circle back a
little shall we
back to the image of my hand squeezing your inner thigh you know
i love getting my hands
on you pressing the tips of my fingers into your bare skin
but not tonight tonight
i want you to do it put your hands on your inner thighs
and squeeze harder
i want to see the marks against your skin oh
sweetheart listen to your whimper and moan for me did it
hurt i bet it
did didn't it
hmm
good
do it again
no
do
yeah
again
that's better now
i suggest you do as i say next time unless
you want that pain to be the least of your worries
after all
you really are such an inviting sight laid bare like this
like spread tits and holes exposed your mouth
ass and cunt all open wide for me to use as i please
you're ready for me to do what
i want aren't
you ready for me to take my place between your thighs and leave
my mark ready for me to pepper
you
with bruises from the pressure of my fingertips to be claimed
by the bite marks
i leave as i move along your skin slowly devouring you
as i inch closer to your soaking eager hole
that's when the real fun begins when my fingers part
those trembling swollen lips and i exhale
focus slut this
isn't time to get lost in your head think about me
about my voice
about what
i might be about to do to you think about how your body
my shivering anticipation as my breath hits
your sole and exposed clit fuck seeing your jump
like that will always make me smile look at the way
you're scorming already
thinking about how your body will try to back away
cursing me as you try to clamp your legs shut
but you can't can you
because although it is a torture
this is a torture that you can't live without you want this
you want me so be a good little toy and open those legs
let me lean close and drag my tongue through your wetness
feel my controlling grip on your thighs
as i take your clip between my teeth
i want you to think about grabbing my hair and grabbing yourself
against my tongue
think about the sounds of your ragged breath
and desperate moans think about grabbing your tears
as you buck hard against my face
but don't you dare think about coming
not until you've proven
you can be a good little slut and earned it
you're going to lie there and focus on me the way
my tongue caresses your clit the way
my lips suckle it gently the way
my grows thunder deep inside you
my grip getting harder as my hunger for you grows
i'm going to take my time pushing you to the edge
holding you there and pulling you back
i'll make you beg me to stop
as my tongue threatens to push you past your limit
put your hands behind your head slut
bite your lip and scorm as you try to resist do whatever
you can to hold that orgasm and keep yourself right
on the edge for me
until i finally pull away
look at you do you even know where you are
you even know what's happening to you
you pour empty headed little slut
look at the way you shiver and moan as i melt you don't worry
this is exactly how i like you
my empty little slut
so just keep lying there and take it it will all be over soon
sweetheart
you just need to be my good girl for a little while longer
you can do that for me can't you
nah
you don't need to speak just nod your head and look at me
with those beautiful vacant eyes
what a pretty little whore
my pretty little whore
just relax
can you feel that
you know what
that is don't you
clever girl
that's my thick hard cock
ready to stretch her desperate little cut
oh i love the way you whimper sweetheart look at me
i said look at me slut
that's it
you look so pretty with my hand against your throat now
tell me what you want what you need
oh well done
like
this
ah fuck
that's it fuck yourself on my cock keep your eyes on mine
that's it
listen to how fucking
why you are for me that dripping cut all nice and ready for me
stretching and taking me so easily like i belong right there
buried inside
you fuck you feel good
oh
i know i know sweetheart not long now okay
just a few more
oh
fuck ah fuck
ugh
that's it come with me
come on my cock
oh fuck i'm coming ugh
don't you dare stop
ugh
that's my girl
啊啊
啊啊啊啊啊啊
啊
啊啊
oh wow
that was ah fuck
hmm
you did such a good job for me sweetheart
such a good girl
taking my instructions such an obedient little princess for me
huh
did you enjoy that good
i'm glad no don't get up you stay there and relax okay
let me go get my good girl some water and then we can cuddle up
you just take it easy i'll be right back
here you go
now getting close
good night
sweetheart
i love you